leaseguide.com 2014-05-10

# Privacy Policy - LeaseGuide.com - Car Lease Guide

Your privacy is important to us.

We respect your privacy and will not use any information we obtain from you or about you in any way other than for the purpose specified. We do not sell, rent, loan, or otherwise share email addresses or other personal information that we may collect from you.

We may use cookies on our website.These are for the purpose of user session management and informational tracking and do not contain personal information unless you provide it. Cookies are stored on your computer and are only accessible to the web site that created the cookie. Other web sites to which we provide links may use their own cookies. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> .  

We use cookies with our optional Lease Kit to save only users' registration codes, which we assign. This is for the convenience of our customers to prevent them from having to remember their code every time they use our Lease Kit. No personal information of any kind is saved in these cookies. We may link to third-party web sites who may use cookies.

We may occasionally offer online polls, surveys, games, quizzes, or questionaires that require that you provide some personal information, but never in such a way that you can be identified. No names, street addresses, email addresses, or telephone numbers will be requested from you for these purposes. Our servers collect domain names and IP addresses for logging purposes.

We may offer various services from other companies who will collect needed personal information from forms placed on our site. This information goes directly to those other companies and is not used, collected, or saved by our company.

For those ordering our optional Lease Kit, we use an outside order processing company that collects only appropriate information about you, including credit card information, to complete your order. This company provides a certified secure connection to their processing systems to protect your personal information and privacy. The information collected is used only for processing your order. We do not collect, use, or save that information ourselves.

Our order processing company sends us emails containing confirmation of orders, including your name, address, and email address. However, these emails do not contain your credit card information. We save the provided information only for possible future order verification and will use the data in no other way.

We use Google ads on our site. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve these ads, which enables it to present ads relevant to the information on our site and other sites you may visit on the Internet. These cookies are used only for informational tracking and contain no personal information about our visitors. Users may opt out of the use of the Google cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Please be aware that LeaseGuide.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites to which we provide links or with which we have business or advertising relationships.

If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, you can contact us at  [Contact - LeaseGuide.com](mailto:contact@leaseguide.com).
